E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
1852-1969
E.P. Dutton (Firm)
89 linear ft.
American publishing firm, founded 1852. Papers include those of founder Edward P. Dutton, John Macrae, and the company's business records, inclucing correspondence, letter books, photographs, clippings, publishers' catalogs, authors' scrapbooks, general files, legal files, financial material, production records, and publicity files.
148957
Biographical History
American book publishing company E. P. Dutton was founded by Edward Payson Dutton in Boston in 1852 as a bookseller. In 1864 Dutton opened a branch office in New York City and in 1869 relocated his headquarters there, where he began publishing as well as selling. In 1906, the company captured an important partner when it became the American distributor of the Everyman's Library series, published by the English firm J. M. Dent.
Dutton remained at the helm of his company until his death in 1923, when he was succeeded by John Macrae (who had started his career at Dutton as an office boy more than forty years before). In 1928, the publishing division was split off into a separate business, E. P. Dutton and Company, Inc., and placed in Macrae's capable hands. E. P. Dutton & Company went on to become one of the leading independent publishers in the United States; authors published included John Hunt, Cleveland Amory, Milton Glaser, Françoise Sagan, Lawrence Durrell, Luigi Pirandello, John Irving, Joyce Carol Oates, Peter Matthiessen, Gavin Maxwell, Gail Sheehy, Ruth Manning-Sanders, La Toya Jackson and Mickey Spillane. Dutton Children's Books is one of the oldest continually operating children's book publishers in the United States whose books include the Winnie-the-Pooh stories.
In 1986, the company was acquired by the Penguin Group and operates now as an imprint of Penguin.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records comprises 21 series: Edward P. Dutton, Memorabilia, Macrae Family, John Macrae files, Publication listings, General files, Authors, Scrapbooks, Legal files, Stocks, Financial, Production files, Publicity files, Foreign correspondence, Children's editor's files, Photographs, News clippings, Letter books, Manufacturing books, Importation books, and Miscellaneous.
The diaries and files of Edward P. Dutton, founder and namesake of the firm, recount the company's growth and development through its first half-century (ca. 1852-1900). Mr. Dutton's Memorabilia includes a map, a journal, and several albums. Some Edward P. Dutton material is also found in the Macrae Family series (see below).
The papers of John Macrae and his descendants, the Macrae family, who ran the company after Dutton's death in 1923, tell of Dutton's growth and direction up through the 1950s. This material includes account books, correspondence, memorabilia, and diaries, as well as numerous items relating to Edward P. Dutton, including correspondence, memorabilia, diaries, and his will.
Publication listings consist of catalogs of books being published for a given topic or a particular season (e.g., Holiday catalogs, Valentine's, childrens books). More than a hundred catalogs span more than 45 years.
General files comprises an assortment of subjects, from agents and authors to publicity schedules.
Authors contains material relating to six particular authors who published with Dutton: Bernt Balchen, Louis Beebe, Phillips Brooks, A. A. Milne, Mark Stein, and Francoise Sagan.
Scrapbooks contains 5 scrapbooks of clippings and other material.
The next three series contain legal and financial material. Legal files include material related to authors, contracts, copyright violations, larceny, name change, royalties, and other legal matters. Stocks consists of minute books, stockholder meeting minutes, account books, and stock ownership information. Financial includes ledgers, advertising records, account books, payroll, order books, and other financial items.
Production files relates to the production of specific titles by Dutton. Titles are given but the author's name is not always listed. At the end of this series are several boxes of book reviews in envelopes, alphabetized by title.
Publicity files contain information about and correspondence with Dutton's authors, including Jane Austen, Aubrey Beardsley, Hilaire Belloc, Algernon Blackwood, Vicente Blasco Ibáñez, Henry James, W. H. Hudson, Leonard Merrick, A. A. Milne, Dhan Gopal Mukerji, Charles G. Norris, W. Lyon Phelps. Luigi Pirandello, Ezra Pound, Katherine Pyle, Montague Summers, Henry Tracy, Jo Van Ammers-Kuller, Gore Vidal, Mary Webb, H. G. Wells, and many more. Other names of interest appearing in the collection include polar explorer Roald Amundsen, artists Boris Artzybasheff and John Vassos, architect Charles Barry, clergyman Phillips Brooks, literary critic and biographer Van Wyck Brooks, journalists John Roy Carlson and Garet Garrett, labor leader Samuel Gompers, British geneticist J.B.S. Haldane, illusionist Harry Houdini, welfare activist Vida Scudder, radiochemist Frederick Soddy, and many more.
Foreign correspondence contains correspondence with authors or publishers (Cape, Dent, Faber & Faber, Methuen, Rainbird, etc) outside the United States.
Children's editor's files consists of material relating specifically to children's books. The first section contains material relating to childrens authors published by Dutton; almost all items give both the name of the author and the title of the book(s) under discussion. Authors represented here include Borghild Dahl ( A Minnetonka Summer, Stowaway to America), Rosalie Fry ( The Mountain Door, The Riddle of the Figurehead), William Campbell Gault, known for his sports books ( Mr. Quarterback, Speedway Challenge), Jean Craighead George ( My Side of the Mountain), Janet Lambert, known for her girls' stories ( Fly Away, Cinda, Wedding Bells, We're Going Steady), A. A. Milne ( Pooh Birthday Book, The World of Pooh), Rita Ritchie ( The Golden Hawks of Genghis Khan, The Year of the Horse), John Schealer (the Zip Zip books), Rosemary Sutcliff ( Beowulf, The Hound of Ulster) and Marguerute Vance, author of historical fiction ( The Empress Josephine, Mary Stuart).
The second section in this series contains information relating to childrens' books in general, for example: American Library Association, book fairs, Children's Book Council, Child Study Association, Horn Book, and nine folders of rejections.
A small number of Photographs are mostly of Edward Dutton and his family.
News clippings concern some of Dutton's authors -- John Ray Carlson, Francoise Sagan -- as well as advertisements and publicity department releases.
Three Letter books contain Country Life Stories, a tribute to John Macrae for fifteen years in advertising (1935), and Acknowledgements.
Manufacturing books and Importation books contain domestic and foreign information, respectively.
A small amount of Miscellaneous material finishes the collection.
Two authors deserve special note. A.A. Milne published his best-selling Winnie the Pooh series in the Unites States with Dutton. This collection contains photographs of Milne's son, Christopher Robin, and the lad's original stuffed animals about which Milne wrote the Pooh books. Also included here is a typescript of Milne's autobiography. The bulk of information relating to Milne is in Milne I through Milne VIII in Publicity files (Box 47), but addition material may be found in Publication listings: The Day's Play by A.A. Milne (Box 9), Authors: Milne, A. A. (Box 11), and Childrens' editors files: Mellin - Milne and Milne-Mudro (Box 77). In addition, Production files contains material on three Milne books: Birthday Party and Other Stories (Box 18), Milne Pop up Book (Box 20), and Peace With Honor (Box 21).
The young French authoress Françoise Sagan published two best sellers, Bonjour Tristesse and A Certain Smile, with Dutton and barnstormed the United States during the mid-1950's on a Dutton publicity tour. The collection contains scrapbooks and correspondence for that campaign. Sagan material may be found in Authors: Sagan (clippings, correspondence, and a story manuscript, Boxes 11 and 12), Production files: book reviews (review of Those Without Shadows, Box 28), and News clippings: Sagan, Françoise (Oversize 2).
Arrangement of the Collection
Arrangement of the series varies. Edward P. Dutton, John Macrae files, and Foreign correspondence are arranged alphabetically by folder title. Publication listings are sorted roughly into categories (general, holiday, calendars, childrens) and within that roughly chronologically.
Authors series is a brief miscellaneous series listed alphabetically by author's name. The 50 boxes of Publicity Files and Children's Editor's Files are also alphabetized by author, but separated into 2-inch-thick handfuls, each filed in a Shaw-Walker folder labeled only with the first and last author in the folder. The inventory below lists the contents of the folders. Out of print books in the Production Files are arranged the same way, in 2-inch-thick handfuls, alphabetized here by the first words of titles. The five boxes of book reviews (Boxes 24-28) list every folder by its complete title. General Files, Legal Files, and Financial Files list every folder title alphabetically.
Remaining series are in no particular order.
The assorted, different-sized bound volumes in Edward P. Dutton (Boxes 3 and 4), Publication Listings (Boxes 7-9), and Financial (Boxes 15-18) are not arranged alphabetically. They follow a logical order by content, chronology, and the way the volumes most sensibly fit in the boxes.
Separated Material
The Shakespeare Memorial Booklet (1864), originally with the collection, has been sent to Rare Books for cataloging and can be located via.
Subject and Genre Headings
Business and Industry; Literature -- American Fiction; Publishing, printing and book arts; Dutton, Edward P.; Macrae, John.; Milne, A. A. (Alan Alexander), 1882-1956.; Sagan, Françoise, 1935-2004.; E.P. Dutton (Firm) -- Archives.; E.P. Dutton (Firm) -- Records and correspondence.; Authors and publishers.; Publishers and publishing -- United States.; Annual reports.; Clippings (information artifacts); Contracts.; Correspondence.; Diaries.; Letter books.; Newsletters.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Publishers' catalogs.; Scrapbooks.; Publishers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Edward P. Dutton
  - Allen - Authors (Box 1)
    Allen, W.B.
    Dutton, E.P. - Account 1900 - et. seq -
    American Booksellers' Association
  - Authors - Big Moose Lake (Box 1)
    Archbishop's Test - Letters form Bishop (1915) Mr. Dutton on books
    Mr. Dutton - Author - Jay - Farran - Satterlee - Hutchington, etc.
    Mr. Dutton - Misc. Authors
    Mr. Dutton's Letters for Authors 1898-1899 etc.
    Dutton E.P. - Big Moose Lake (1860's?)
  - Book of the Month Club (Box 1)
  - Booksellers - Congress (Box 1)
    Bookseller Announcements
    Booksellers Breutauos
    #1 Booksellers - Letters to - From Mr. Macrae - Various Matters
    Re Breutaous's
    Congress Miscellaneous
  - Copyright (Box 1)
    Re Congress Conpyright 1930-31
    Publisher's Affairs Copyright
  - Corres. Creditors - Dutton, Julia (Box 1)
    Creditor's Protective Committee of Bretanous's Inc.
    Dutton Bulletin, Letter on
    Macrae, John - Francis Bird Dutton
    Dutton, E.P. Letters Concerning Julia S. Dutton - including her will - (Mrs. E.P. Dutton) Julia Sleeper Dutton
  - Dutton, Martha - Doane (Box 1)
    Dutton, Martha S.
    Dutton, Dr. Julia (EPD's sister)
    Mr. Dutton and Elbridge Brooks (Master of the Strong Hearts) etc.
    Channing, William Elley - Dutton and Wentworth
    Dutton, E.P. Correspondence with clergymen
    Dutton, E.P. as critic
    Dutton, E.P. letter at death
    E.P. Dutton Bishop Doane
  - Employees - Family (Box 1)
    Dutton, E.P. Employees and Co.
    Dutton, E.P. Family Mr. Dutton - family affairs - VERY PERSONAL (Many birthday greeting of several years)
  - Family (Box 1)
    Dutton, E.P. letter to his parents for Europe
    Julia Sleeper Mrs Dutton family Affairs - VERY PERSONAL - Will and Estate Settlements
    Mr. Dutton Family Affairs - VERY PERSONAL - including: Horance Dutton, Frances Dutton (Mrs. H), Martha Dutton, F. W. Bird Estate
  - Family - Harper (Box 1)
    Dutton, E.P. Family letters 1860-1866 Personal from his father (Geo D.) and a cousin
    Re - Graphic Art Code
    Dutton, E.P. (Library) Fellowship 1930
    Dutton, E.P. - J.W. Harper
    Dutton, E.P. Family - Will Harper
  - Harper - Howarth (Box 1)
    Dutton, E.P. - 1920 article by J.A. Holden of Pub. Wkly
    Halt, Henry to John Macrae
    Howarth, F.M. Correspondence with Mr. Dutton
  - Huntington - Ide (Box 1)
    Huntington, Bishop Letter of Mr. Dutton and Items
    Huntington, W.R.
    Ide, Fannie Ogden Letter a critic 1887
    Ide and Dutton announcements 1852-1855
  - Inventories, Dutton, E.P. - Personal - Inventories of Ridgefield, Conn. and NYC homes (Box 2)
  - Investments, Dutton, Mr. E.P. Personal Investments (Box 2)
  - Investments - Library (Box 2)
    Investments
    Joint Board of Publishers and Booksellers
    Jordan, Charolette B. - Correspondence with Mr. E.P. Dutton, 1897-1898 on Sphinx Lore
    Launt, Rev. F.A.D. - E.P. Dutton 1900-1901
    Library Correspondence World War I Mr. Nacrae
  - Library - Macrae (Box 2)
    Re - Library Scholarships
    Publishers Affairs
    Library Correspondence Mr. Macrae
    Dutton, E.P. - John Macrae (1907-1917)
    John Macrae - VERY PERSONAL Correspondence with Mr. E.P. Dutton (1913-1918)
  - Macrae - Moulton (Box 2)
    Mr. Dutton and Mr. Macrae - 1918-1921
    Macrae, John Booksellers Parker-Los Angeles
    Macrae, John Letter from Mr. Dutton's relatives acknowledging books, etc.
    Macrae, John Personal letters of condolence (or death in firm to fellow publishers
    Mr. Dutton and Mr. Macare - 1901-1921 - Reorganization of firm
    Mr. Dutton - C.C. Moon 1893-1895
    Dutton, E.P. - Corres. with Rev. Arthur Moulton 1907
  - National Association of Book Publishers (Box 2)
  - National Association of Book Publishers I, National Association of Book Publishers - Bull. 1926 Mr. Macrae President (Box 2)
  - National Association of Book Publishers II, 1931-1932 (Box 2)
  - National Association of Book Publishers III (Box 2)
  - National Association of Book Publishers IV (Box 2)
  - National Association of Book Publishers V (Box 2)
    Letters, documents, notices, etc. including copyright business Jan. and Feb. 1931; Copyright
  - National Association of Book Publishers VI, Copyright (Box 2)
  - National Association of Book Publishers VII, 1920s (Box 3)
  - National Booksellers Code - Photos (Box 3)
    (untitled folder)
    Dutton, Mr. E.P. - Personal
    Photographs of Mr. and Mrs. Dutton - Note envelope
    Dutton staff photos Publishers' Lunch Club
    Dutton (E.P.) - Photos
    Dutton (E.P.) - Politics
    Potter, Henry C. - Sermon sent to Mr. Dutton by Bishop Potter
    Friends of Princeton Library
    A letter to an English Publisher from Mr. Dutton (John F. Shaw Co.)
    Publisher's Lunch Club
  - Publisher's Weekly - Ridgefield (Box 3)
    Publisher's Weekly 1919-1920s Frederic Melcher
    Mr. Dutton and Katherine Pyle
    Dutton, E.P. - Rodgefield, Conn. home and equipment
  - Ridgefield - Scudder (Box 3)
    Dutton, E.P. Ridgefield, Conn. Library Assoc.
    Ryan Thoman (1899) Recollections of an Old Musician
    Scudder, Vidda - On Mr. Dutton
  - Sleeper (Box 3)
    Sleeper family - Mrs. Elizabeth Sleeper Davis
    Sleeper, Jacob - Material on and other Sleeper obits also Sleeper will
  - Untitled (Box 3)
    Swayne, Edward C. (1890) Letter from ...
    1854 - G. Glympse of Boston Society, George Ticknor and E.P. Dutton - town hall a name use of
    Dutton, E.P. Arthur Woods (nephew)
    Young, Charolette M. Correspondence (1861)
  - Book - Letters (Box 3)
  - Book - Shipman's No. 3 Duplicating Letter Book (Box 3)
- Memorabilia
  - Map - of Rome - possibly used by Mr. Dutton on 1851? (Box 3)
  - Centennial Scraps Album (Box 3)
  - Journal (Box 3)
  - Book - executive Committee Minutes, 1859 (Box 3)
  - Photo Album - "On The Ridge" Ridgefield, Conn. (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook (Box 3)
- Macrae Family
  - Dutton, Edward P. - Will (Box 4)
  - Book - Personal Accounts, July 6, 1907 - April 3, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Book - Wholesale Accounts, Feb. 1, 1899 - May 1, 1907 (Box 4)
  - Book - Accounts, Jan. 1, 1856 - Feb. 2, 1856 (Box 4)
  - Book - "The Equitable Trust Company of New York" account book (Box 4)
  - Book - Personal accounts, 1857 (Box 4)
  - Books - 21 - Personal Accounts and Addresses, 1879-1899 (Box 4)
  - Book - Accounts (Box 4)
  - Book - Accounts (Box 4)
  - Book - Cash, CPD E.P. Dutton, Jan. 1, 1867 (Box 4)
  - Book - Copies of E.P. Dutton Business Letters, June 15, 1877 - August 22, 1881 (Box 4)
  - Book - Record of Books and items, 1895-1907 (Box 4)
  - Book - E.P. Dutton Cash records and some stock records, Oct. 27. 1894 - Jan. 2, 1908 (Box 4)
  - Book - "Every Day" text, hymn, prayer, and record for every day in the year (Box 4)
  - Book - New Testament Psalms (Box 4)
  - Book - "The Book of Common Prayer" belonging to E.P. Dutton (Box 4)
  - Envelope - Memorabilia - Keys (2 sets) and wedding ring (Box 4)
  - Envelope - Memorabilia - E.P. Dutton Business Cards, Wallet (Box 4)
  - Envelope - Memorabilia - Doll designs and models (Box 4)
  - Books - E.P. Dutton Diaries, 1910-1918; 1920 (Box 4)
  - Books - E.P. Dutton Diaries, 1880's (Box 4)
  - Daily Memorando January, 1879 (Box 4)
  - Book - Diaries 1870 to 1879; Acts and expenses - trip to England 1870 - two years only (Box 4)
  - Books - E.P. Dutton Diaries, 1890s (Box 4)
  - Books - E.P. Dutton Diaries, 1900-1909 (Box 4)
  - Book - Works of George Eliot Vol. 1 Adam - Bede (Box 4)
  - Book - Accounts, Jan. 17, 1867 - July 3. 1880 (Box 4)
  - Book - E.P. Dutton Accounts (Box 4)
  - Book - Accounts (Box 4)
  - Book - Family Laundry List (Box 4)
  - Book - Records (Box 4)
  - American - Autobiography (Box 5)
    American Institute of Graphic Arts; corres., fliers, insurance policy
    50th Anniversary; corres.
    Autobiography; corres., printed copy of biog. 75 pgs.
    Autobiography, Ms; 77 pages Memo to Midwestern Library Association
  - Book Clubs and Corres., clippings, flyers (Box 5)
  - Book of the Month Club I (Box 5)
    Booksellers Letters; corres., clippings
    Circulars sent out, etc.; fliers, pamphlets
    Book of the Month Club fight - News stories; clippings Book of the Month Club II
    letters from editors, publishers and other corres.
    letters from Judges; corres.
  - Book of the Month Club III (Box 5)
    Literary Editors and Col. Stories - also editorials; clippings, fliers
    Releases on fight; legal doc's
  - Bradford - Civic Duties (Box 5)
    Bradford, Gamaliel; corres.
    Literary Reviews, Millen Brand; corres.
    Personal - Kessler Cartoon; corres.
    Fishing Cartoons by Ryan Walker; corres.
    Civic Duties; corres.
  - Clippings, Clippings; clippings, corres. (Box 5)
  - Clubs - Death (Box 5)
    Clubs and Societies; corres., clippings
    Memberships, clubs, etc.; corres.
    Curious Requests; corres.
    Letters and cables from Eng. Publishers and Agents
    Letters at time of Death - EBM and JM, Jr.
  - Death I, Letters at time of Death JM, Jr.; Letters at time of Death EBM (Box 5)
  - Death II, Letters at time of Death Opal Macrae (Box 5)
  - Death III, Letters at time of Death EBM and JM, Jr. (Box 5)
- John Macrae files
  - Death News Clippings, obituaries, corres., list of names and addresses (Box 6)
  - Dinners - Dutton (Box 6)
    Dinners, Receptions, Affairs (Invitations and Acknowledgements) Katherine Metcalf Roos
    Documents, Letters Organization, WE Cashin and Mrs. Josy Swift
    Dutton, E.P. - Estate Settlement 1928 corres., stocks, legal documents
    Dutton, E.P. and Co. Bal. Sheets and Statements 1905-1912
  - Dutton (Box 6)
    Dutton, E.P. and Co. Documents in re. Inc. 1901-1902
    Mr. Dutton 1919 New Stock of firm, corres. w/Grenville Clark and Henry Smith
    Dutton, E.P. and Co. Estate Settlement corres.
  - Eulogy, New York Times, Wednesday, February 23, 1944; article on John Macrae (Box 6)
  - Gifts - Little (Box 6)
    Misc. Gifts to this person and that; books, cards sent, donations, corres.
    Lindberg, Charles - 1931 Books he asked for - corres.
    Literary editors 1920s Letters to and from John Macrae
    Literary reviews Editors Macrae's letters to editors
    J.J. Little and Ires Co.
  - John Macrae Fellowship - Opal Macrae (Box 6)
    John Macrae Fellowship Suggestions corres., misc.
    EBM - Business Correspondence; mostly corres. b/w E.M. and J.M. during E.M.'s 1931 trip to London; business and personal
    Macrae, John - John Jr. - business corres.
    Macrae, Elliot - misc. corres.
    Macrae, Opal Wheeler; photos, corres., reviews, announcements
  - Manuscripts (Box 6)
    Macrae, John Memorial Service 1947
    Macrae, John Manuscripts belonging to: corres.
    Newspapers corres. misc. papers and editors
  - Newspapers, corres., misc. Newspapers and editors (Box 6)
  - Passports - Protest (Box 6)
    Passports John Macrae 1920-1937
    John Macrae - corres. in re passports and visas
    John A. Post (Re. "Automobile Liability")
    Macrae, John Letters of Congratulation - presiding EPD 1928
    Letters of Protest - misc.
  - Reorganization, 1928; Legal documents and corres. (Box 6)
  - Reviews - Sales (Box 6)
    Reviews; clippings, corres.
    Root, Clark, Buckner and Ballantine; corres.
    Root, Clark, Buckner and Ballantine, re: Income Tax; corres.
    Sale, Possible, 1928
  - Sarage - Smith (Box 6)
    Reverend Theodore F. Sarage, corres.
    Smith, Mr. Henry Chapp 1910 - 1928 (EPD and JM); corres.
  - Smith - World War I (Box 6)
    Smith, Henry Clapp 1929-1936; corres.
    Smith, Joseph S.; corres.
    Theatre (taste); corres.
    "Turning from the Past Toward the Future" - 1932; corres.
    World War I; corres.
- Publication listings
  - Catalogue 1877 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1881 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1883-1884 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1884 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1885 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1886 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1887 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1888 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1889, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1890 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1891, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1892, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1893, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1894, 4 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1895, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1896, 3 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1897, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1898 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1899, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1900, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1901 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1902, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1903, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1904 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1905 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1906 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1907, 3 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1908 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1910 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1911, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1912 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1913, 3 copies (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1914, 2 copies - 1 copy in folder (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1915 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1916, 2 copies - 1 copy in folder (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1917 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1919, in folder (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1922 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1926 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1926 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1927 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1928 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1928 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1928 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1929 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1930 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1932 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1933 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1934 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue 1935 (Box 7)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1936; 2 copies (Box 8)